[{"answer": "I absolutely do, especially if she's terrified having seen quite possibly what happened to her mother and possibly her kid brother, and she's in the clutches of this man.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "The longer this goes on do you get a bigger sense of foreboding about what may have happened to Hannah?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Well, they're talking about possibly a garden.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Will they build any kind of new property there?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "You know, I just think it's a wonderful way of putting this all behind and starting to move forward.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is your reaction, first of all, to the scenes in Cleveland?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think everyone's journey through that recovery is different.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "And given the awful experience that you had to endure as a father, and it ended obviously happily for you but ends disastrously for so many, given that it ended well and it has done for these three victims in Cleveland, what is the best advice you would give them and indeed their families around them for how they can make a proper recovery?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "You know, my -- my advice is to stay positive and to, you know, just keep the pressure on.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "But what can you say to him?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "From the sounds of it, it comes across as a tragic recipe of disaster.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Is that your understanding of what happened here?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, in the wild scenario, the ecosystem where this creature lives, they are known as being an aggressive species of snake.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "I mean, is it the kind of thing that that kind of African rock python would do if it got out of the cage and found itself near two young boys like that?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "I think it's only in specialized situations should private citizens have large snakes like this.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "Should anybody have these kind of things in a home environment (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "ORWIN: It is -- Piers, it's very quite possible.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Are we now seeing some of the more deadly effects of global warming on the wildlife in the arctic?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I -- I have.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "You changed your mind?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I'm surprised.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "So when -- when New York Mayor Bloomberg was reported to say medical marijuana is the greatest hoax of all time, what do you say to that?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Within like the first five minutes.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "How quickly do you expect this to work?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, look, the -- it can be difficult to -- to sort of stratify the legitimate patients who have use for cannabis, not only as a medication but as the only medication for their sufferings.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Sanjay?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I -- I think so.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Why (ph) -- isn't there an inconsistency in government policy?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "I have -- I have tried it.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Have you tried it?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the irony isn't in some ways because I work on this documentary.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "Well, what effect did it have on you compared to, say, drinking alcohol or whatever?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Why do we want to support that?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Yes, yes, I am.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Tough guy now?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "It is my British humor.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Is that British humor?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "You know, I think whether or not he is, isn't really the question.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Should he still be campaigning against this woman that you've supported today?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "You know, Anthony Weiner is asking New Yorkers for a second chance.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 570, "question": "Or is he talking a lot about bunk (ph)?", "qSentId": 569}, {"answer": "But look, this is a serious job.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Third chance?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well, I think what this reminds us of is that when you take on a position like mayor of New York, you're a role model in one respect or another.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Is he trivializing just by staying in the race, given all that's been going on?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I felt good about my chances from day one.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Your chances have got significantly better with Anthony Weiner's latest mishap, haven't (ph) they (ph)?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Disgraceful.", "docId": "130807pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Do you think, as I do, that he's one of the great cheats in sporting history and should be kicked out of baseball?", "qSentId": 618}]